Guide to the Institute on the Arts and Civic Dialogue Archive MSS.127
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 1: 1997-1998, 59265
  - Subseries 1.5: Discussion Materials and Transcripts, 59266
    - Transcripts: Robert Brunstein, 7/98, 1998; 59270 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Transcripts: Shu Lea Cheang, 8/12/98, 1998; 59269 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Photographs: Discussion Panels, 1998; 59268 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Photographs: Discussion Panels, 1998; 59267 (Box 3, Folder 137)
- Series 2: 1999, 58729
  These files document the second season of the institute in a manner similar to the previous series. Apart from the alphabetical administrative files, there are discrete sets of files relating to the intern program, a large body of email correspondence, and a summary report of all the year's activities.
  - Subseries 2.1: Administrative Files, 59080
    These files are arranged alphabetically by folder title and comprise the main records of administrative activity of 1999. Included are resumes, job applications and other files relating to administrative staffing, budget information, fax correspondence, and records relating to space planning, guest accommodations, and other facets of planning.
    - Advertising, 1999; 59264 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Artists Abstracts and Information, undated; 59263 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Budget Breakdown per Company or Artist, undated; 59262 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Call to Artists: Contact Institutions, 1999; 59261 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Call to Artists: Questions and Requests, 1999; 59260 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Call to Artists: Correspondence, 1999; 59259 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Call to Interns, 1999; 59258 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Call to Scholars, 1999; 59257 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Call for Papers: Request for Applications, 1999; 59256 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Casual Employee: Dong, Chinnie, undated; 59255 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Casual Employee: Frasier, Dionne, undated; 59254 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Casual Employee: Gonzales, Andrea, undated; 59253 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Casual Employee: Harvard Temp service, undated; 59252 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Casual Employee: Hickey, Kirsten, undated; 59251 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Casual Employee: Medeiros, Maria, undated; 59250 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Casual Employee: O'Connell, Nathaniel, undated; 59249 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Casual Employee: Tan, Michael, undated; 59248 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Catering Closing Party, 1999; 59247 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Catering Picnic, 1999; 59246 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Center for Training and Development, undated; 59245 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Company and Teachers, 1999; 59244 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Computers for 1430 Mass. Ave, undated; 59243 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Computers: "Bit by Bit" Rentals, 1999; 59242 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Consulting Services: Artist/Scholar Program Consultant, undated; 59241 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Consultant Services: Issacson Miller (Headhunter), undated; 59240 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Consulting Services: Page, Liz, undated; 59239 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Consulting Services: Payments, 1999; 59238 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Contacts and Network, undated; 59237 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Current Job Descriptions, 1999; 59236 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Deputy Director Search: Candidates, undated; 59235 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Deputy Director Search: Interviews (Prior), undated; 59234 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Deputy Director Search: Letters Informing Candidates of Prolonged Selection Process, undated; 59233 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Deputy Director Search: NYC Interviews 1/15-1/16, 1999; 59232 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Deputy Director Search: Rejection Letters, 1999; 59231 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Deputy Director Search: Resumes, 1999; 59230 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Deputy Director Search: Resumes, 1999; 59229 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Deputy Director Search: Resumes, 1999; 59228 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Deputy Director Search: Resumes, 1999; 59227 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Dinners: Number of Participants, undated; 59226 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Directions to the City, undated; 59225 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Directory of Summer Participants, 1999; 59224 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Du Bois Correspondence, memos, undated; 59223 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Du Bois Staff List, undated; 59222 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Employees and Participants: Rivers, Stephen, undated; 59221 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Employees and Participants: Chalian, David, undated; 59220 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Equipment, undated; 59219 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Equipment: Audiovisual Rentals, undated; 59218 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Equipment: Estimated Costs, undated; 59217 (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - Event Schedule, 1999; 59216 (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - Evening Schedule, undated; 59215 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - Fax Chronology #1, 1998; 59214 (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - Fax Chronology #2, 1998; 59213 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - Fax Chronology #2, 1998; 59212 (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - Faxes, Communications, and Reading Notes, undated; 59211 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - Fax Cover Sheets, undated; 59210 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Fax Machine, 1999; 59209 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - Feedback: Audience Evaluation Form, 1999; 59208 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Feedback: Core Audience Questionnaire, undated; 59207 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - Feedback: Staff Evaluation, 1999; 59206 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - Feedback: Responses from Dorothy Channing, undated; 59205 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - Feedback: Unmediated Evaluations/Responses, undated; 59204 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - Financial: Alien Payment Information Form, undated; 59203 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - Financial: Budget, 1999; 59202 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - Financial: Computer Finance, 1999; 59201 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - Financial: Credit Vouchers, 1999; 59200 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - Financial: Donations, 1999; 59199 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - Financial: Extra Compensation Requests, 1999; 59198 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - Financial: Expense Report Copies (Mauzy), undated; 59197 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - Financial: General Correspondence, undated; 59196 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - Financial: Keyform Orders, undated; 59195 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - Fund-Raising Guidelines, 1999; 59194 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - General Information, undated; 59193 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Graphic Design: Web Page, undated; 59192 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Graphic Design: Brochure, undated; 59191 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Graphic Design: Stationery/Website Correspondence, undated; 59190 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Graphic Design: Designers, undated; 59189 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Housing Agreement: 18 Bank Street #503, undated; 59188 (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Housing Agreement: 19 Centre St #2, undated; 59187 (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Housing Agreement: 50 Follen St #301, undated; 59186 (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - Housing Agreement: 1572 Mass Ave #5, undated; 59185 (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Housing Agreement: 65 Mt Auburn St. #65, undated; 59184 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Housekeeping: Memos from Carol MacLeod, undated; 59183 (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Hotels: Charles Hotel, Art Spiegelman, undated; 59182 (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - Hotels: Charles Hotel Information, undated; 59181 (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - Hotels: Charles Hotel, Convening, undated; 59180 (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - Hotels: Doubletree Hotel, undated; 59179 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Hotel Information General, undated; 59178 (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - Hotels: Inn at Harvard, undated; 59177 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - Hotels: University Park Hotel at MIT, undated; 59176 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - Interim Personnel, 1999; 59175 (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Internal/Co. Info, undated; 59174 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Invocation, undated; 59173 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Invoices: 1998 Invoice Copies (processed), 59172 (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - Invoices sent to ART for Payment, undated; 59171 (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - Job Openings: Miscellaneous, 1999; 59170 (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - Job Openings: Staff, undated; 59169 (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - Job Positions: Staff/Participant Recruitment, 1999; 59168 (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - Job Positions: Staff Descriptions, undated; 59167 (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - Job Positions: Rejected Resumes, 1999; 59166 (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - Maps--Harvard, undated; 59165 (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - Meeting Notes: Planning Retreat, 9/98, 1998; 59164 (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - Miscellaneous Artist Correspondence, undated; 59163 (Box 4, Folder 239)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1999; 59162 (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - Miscellaneous Girls' Writings, undated; 59161 (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - Miscellaneous Resumes, undated; 59160 (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - Orientation Notes, 1999; 59159 (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - Organizational Charts, 1999; 59158 (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - Other Equipment: Crimson Cash Copy Card, undated; 59157 (Box 4, Folder 245)
    - Other Equipment: Pagers, undated; 59156 (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - Panels and Panelists, 1999; 59155 (Box 4, Folder 247)
    - Participants, 248; 59154 (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - Phone Scripts; List for Core Audience and Fraternal Organizations, List of Participants, List of Contacts, undated; 59153 (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - Phones: Anna Deavere Smith's AT and T Calling Card, undated; 59152 (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - Telephone Bills, 1999; 59151 (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - Phones: Cellular Phone Rentals, 1999; 59150 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - Phones: Phone Manual, undated; 59149 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - Phones: Voice Mail, 1999; 59148 (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - Phones: Phone Issues, undated; 59147 (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Press Release, 1999; 59146 (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - Press Clippings, undated; 59145 (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Press Correspondence, undated; 59144 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - Proposal for Collaboration: The Cambridge Multi-Cultural Arts Center, undated; 59143 (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Proposed Associations: Boal, Augusto, undated; 59142 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - "Producer of the Public" Position, Correspondence, 1999; 59141 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - Public Conversations and Production Budget, undated; 59140 (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - Purchase Orders, undated; 59139 (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - Purchase Orders: Requisitions, undated; 59138 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - Purchase Orders: Requisitions (Copies), undated; 59137 (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - Receipts, undated; 59136 (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - Rehearsal Schedule and Notes, undated; 59135 (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - Rehearsal Schedule for the Institute Company, undated; 59134 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Rehearsal Space/Studio Information, undated; 59133 (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Reports: Ciuberkis' Suggestions for IACD and ART, undated; 59132 (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Reports: Gardener, Howard, undated; 59131 (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - Reports: Project Zero Report, 9/9/98, 1998; 59130 (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - Reports: Weekly Status, undated; 59129 (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - Request for Reimbursement, 1999; 59128 (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - Requests: Archival Access, undated; 59127 (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - Requests: Barker Room, undated; 59126 (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - Requests: Core Audience, undated; 59125 (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - Requests: Meetings, undated; 59124 (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - Requests: Scheduling, undated; 59123 (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Requests: Miscellaneous, undated; 59122 (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - Schedule of Performances and Presentations, undated; 59121 (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Schedules/Residencies, undated; 59120 (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - Scholars Attending Panels, undated; 59119 (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - Special Guests, undated; 59118 (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - Staff and Staff Meetings, undated; 59117 (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - Staffing, undated; 59116 (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - Staff/Artists' Meetings, NYC, May 1-2, 1999, 59115 (Box 4, Folder 287)
    - Staff Contact Sheets and Information, undated; 59114 (Box 4, Folder 288)
    - Staff Information, undated; 59113 (Box 4, Folder 289)
    - State and Regional Arts Agencies Listings (from NEA), undated; 59112 (Box 4, Folder 290)
    - Yellow Voucher Checks, 1999; 59111 (Box 4, Folder 291)
    - Taxes: Certificate of Exemption, undated; 59110 (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - Taxes: Tax Identification Number, undated; 59109 (Box 4, Folder 293)
    - Teleconference: Fundraising, undated; 59108 (Box 5, Folder 294)
    - Telephone Meetings With Anna Deavere Smith, undated; 59107 (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - Tony Newfield's Company List, undated; 59106 (Box 5, Folder 296)
    - Training for Facilitators of Core Group Audience Response Panels; Feedback from Core Audiences, undated; 59105 (Box 5, Folder 297)
    - Travel, 1999; 59104 (Box 5, Folder 298)
    - Travel Expense Reports: A-B, undated; 59103 (Box 5, Folder 299)
    - Travel Expense Reports: C-D, undated; 59102 (Box 5, Folder 300)
    - Travel Expense Reports: E-H, undated; 59101 (Box 5, Folder 301)
    - Travel Expense Reports: I-N, undated; 59100 (Box 5, Folder 302)
    - Travel Expense Reports: O-Z, undated; 59099 (Box 5, Folder 303)
    - Vendor (Corporate) Invoice Coding From, undated; 59098 (Box 5, Folder 304)
    - General Travel Information, undated; 59097 (Box 5, Folder 305)
    - Vendor Information: Boston Coach, undated; 59096 (Box 5, Folder 306)
    - Vendor Information: Cambridge Radio Dispatch Services, undated; 59095 (Box 5, Folder 307)
    - Vendor Information: Don West (Photographer), undated; 59094 (Box 5, Folder 308)
    - Vendor Information: Harvard Faculty Club, undated; 59093 (Box 5, Folder 309)
    - Vendor Information: New England Conservatory, undated; 59092 (Box 5, Folder 310)
    - Vendor Information: Hipster Entertainment; Anna Deavere Smith's Stay in New York, December 1998, 59091 (Box 5, Folder 311)
    - Vendor Information: Northern Light Productions, undated; 59090 (Box 5, Folder 312)
    - Vendor Information: Staples Business, undated; 59089 (Box 5, Folder 313)
    - Vendor Information: Town Office Supply, undated; 59088 (Box 5, Folder 314)
    - Vendor Information: Vocell Bus Company, undated; 59087 (Box 5, Folder 315)
    - Vendor Information: Harvard Venue Information, undated; 59086 (Box 5, Folder 316)
    - Venues: Theater Policy Book for Non-Harvard Affiliates, undated; 59085 (Box 5, Folder 317)
    - VIP Welcome Letters and Info on Steering Committees, undated; 59084 (Box 5, Folder 318)
    - Web Page Materials (Including Requests to Revise IACD site), 1999; 59083 (Box 5, Folder 319)
    - Welcome Letter, 1999; 59082 (Box 5, Folder 320)
    - Welcome Package, 1999; 59081 (Box 5, Folder 321)
  - Subseries 2.2: Intern Records, 59050
    This series of records deals exclusively with the intern program for the 1999 session at the Institute: their hiring and activities, housing and other administrative details. This series of files constituted a distinct group for 1999 where in other years intern records were integrated into the main administrative files. Folders are as found, loosely arranged by topic.
    - Intern Request Forms, undated; 59079 (Box 5, Folder 322)
    - Venus O. Reese, undated; 59078 (Box 5, Folder 323)
    - Intern Information, undated; 59077 (Box 5, Folder 324)
    - Intern Correspondence, undated; 59076 (Box 5, Folder 325)
    - Intern Program Coordinator, undated; 59075 (Box 5, Folder 326)
    - Interns and Intern Related Issues, 1999; 59074 (Box 5, Folder 327)
    - Call to Interns, 1999; 59073 (Box 5, Folder 328)
    - Intern Application: Bryant, Shannon (Hired), 1999; 59072 (Box 5, Folder 329)
    - Intern Application: Cheesman, Alison (Hired), 1999; 59071 (Box 5, Folder 330)
    - Intern Application: Cott, Emma (Hired), 1999; 59070 (Box 5, Folder 331)
    - Intern Application: Gibbon, Amanda (Hired), 1999; 59069 (Box 5, Folder 332)
    - Intern Application: Ginsburg, Steve (Hired), 1999; 59068 (Box 5, Folder 333)
    - Intern Application: Kalghatgi, Jutika (Hired), 1999; 59067 (Box 5, Folder 334)
    - Intern Application: Kertzner, Daniel (Hired), 1999; 59066 (Box 5, Folder 335)
    - Intern Application: Kornelly, Sharon (Hired), 1999; 59065 (Box 5, Folder 336)
    - Intern Application: McNiff, Fiona (Hired), 1999; 59064 (Box 5, Folder 337)
    - Intern Application: Millman, Sierra (Hired), 1999; 59063 (Box 5, Folder 338)
    - Intern Application: Shassanni, Jason (Hired), 1999; 59062 (Box 5, Folder 339)
    - Intern Application: Turnbull, John (Hired), 1999; 59061 (Box 5, Folder 340)
    - Intern Application: Wilensky-Lanford, Brooke (Hired), 1999; 59060 (Box 5, Folder 341)
    - Intern Application: Yee, Pei (Hired), 1999; 59059 (Box 5, Folder 342)
    - Incomplete Intern Applications, 1999; 59058 (Box 5, Folder 343)
    - Intern Candidate Forwarded by ART, undated; 59057 (Box 5, Folder 344)
    - Intern Coordinator Position/Responsibilities, 1999; 59056 (Box 5, Folder 345)
    - Intern Recruitment/Acceptance Process, undated; 59055 (Box 5, Folder 346)
    - Rejections: Interns, undated; 59054 (Box 5, Folder 347)
    - Intern Applications--Rejected, D-K, undated; 59053 (Box 5, Folder 348)
    - Intern Applications--Rejected, L-V, undated; 59052 (Box 5, Folder 349)
    - Volunteers, 1999; 59051 (Box 5, Folder 350)
  - Subseries 2.3: Correspondence and Email, 59028
    This series contains various folders of correspondence arranged by various topics but the bulk of the series is printouts of email to and from Anna McDonald. The email is arranged chronologically by month and divided into incoming and outgoing sections.
    - Correspondence: Anthony Newfield, Director of Company Relations, undated; 59049 (Box 5, Folder 351)
    - Correspondence: Anna McDonald's Correspondence Chronology, 1998; 59048 (Box 5, Folder 352)
    - Correspondence: Core Audience, undated; 59047 (Box 5, Folder 353)
    - Correspondence: Call to Core Audience, undated; 59046 (Box 5, Folder 354)
    - Correspondence: General, undated; 59045 (Box 5, Folder 355)
    - Correspondence: Thank You Letter, undated; 59044 (Box 5, Folder 356)
    - Email: Incoming, January, 1999; 59043 (Box 5, Folder 357)
    - Email: Outgoing, January, 1999; 59042 (Box 5, Folder 358)
    - Email: Incoming, February, 1999; 59041 (Box 5, Folder 359)
    - Email: Outgoing, February, 1999; 59040 (Box 5, Folder 360)
    - Email: Incoming, March, 1999; 59039 (Box 5, Folder 361)
    - Email: Outgoing, March, 1999; 59038 (Box 5, Folder 362)
    - Email: Incoming, April, 1999; 59037 (Box 5, Folder 363)
    - Email: Outgoing, April, 1999; 59036 (Box 5, Folder 364)
    - Email: Incoming, May, 1999; 59035 (Box 5, Folder 365)
    - Email: Outgoing, May, 1999; 59034 (Box 5, Folder 366)
    - Email: Incoming, June, 1999; 59033 (Box 5, Folder 367)
    - Email: Outgoing, June, 1999; 59032 (Box 5, Folder 368)
    - Email: Incoming, July, 1999; 59031 (Box 5, Folder 369)
    - Email: Outgoing, July, 1999; 59030 (Box 6, Folder 370)
    - Email: Incoming, August, 1999; 59029 (Box 6, Folder 371)
  - Subseries 2.4: Files of Anna Deavere Smith, 59016
    This small series is composed of miscellaneous files reflecting activities of Anna Deavere Smith. They include correspondence, expenses, schedules and written pieces.
    - Theater Company, undated; 59027 (Box 6, Folder 372)
    - Email Chronology #1, 1999; 59026 (Box 6, Folder 373)
    - Email Chronology #2, 1999; 59025 (Box 6, Folder 374)
    - Other Correspondence, 1999; 59024 (Box 6, Folder 375)
    - Requests/Correspondence Forwarded to San Francisco, undated; 59023 (Box 6, Folder 376)
    - Correspondence with Marty Mauzy, 1999; 59022 (Box 6, Folder 377)
    - Business/IACD Expenses and Reimbursements, 1999; 59021 (Box 6, Folder 378)
    - Call Letters, Schedule, 1999; 59020 (Box 6, Folder 379)
    - Chronology File, 1999; 59019 (Box 6, Folder 380)
    - Meeting at James Irvine Foundation (Correspondence), undated; 59018 (Box 6, Folder 381)
    - Handwritten Introduction to Common Infractions/Gross Injustices, 1999; 59017 (Box 6, Folder 382)
  - Subseries 2.5: Artist Overviews, 58972
    This file contains records on artists and works created or developed at the Institute in 1999. Materials include correspondence, budgets, descriptions and summaries, artist biographies and promotional material.
    - Promotional Material and Artist Biographies: Common Infractions/Gross Injustices, Written by Anna Deavere Smith, undated; 59015 (Box 6, Folder 383)
    - Artist Overview: Anna Deavere Smith with Liz Diamond, undated; 59014 (Box 6, Folder 384)
    - Artist Overview: Lee Breuer and Mabou Mines Theater Company, 1999; 59013 (Box 6, Folder 385)
    - Artist Overview: Demetria Royals, Anita Gonzalez, and Robbie McCauley, Mother Courage, undated; 59012 (Box 6, Folder 386)
    - Artist Overview: Lee Breuer Ecco Porco, undated; 59011 (Box 6, Folder 387)
    - Artist Overview: McCallum, Bradley, Witness, undated; 59010 (Box 6, Folder 388)
    - Artist Overview: Sissako, Abderrahmane, Life on Earth, undated; 59009 (Box 6, Folder 389)
    - Artist Overview: Art Spiegelman, Drawn to Death, undated; 59008 (Box 6, Folder 390)
    - Artist Overview: Conway and Pratt, The Small Museum of Women's Experience, undated; 59007 (Box 6, Folder 391)
    - Conway and Pratt Correspondence, undated; 59006 (Box 6, Folder 392)
    - Artist Overview: Girl's Choir of Harlem, 1999; 59005 (Box 6, Folder 393)
    - Girl's Choir of Harlem Correspondence, undated; 59004 (Box 6, Folder 394)
    - Artist Overview: Arben Kumbaro, Disremember Me, undated; 59003 (Box 6, Folder 395)
    - Kumbaro, Ben: Disremember Me Prop List, Rehearsal Notes, Visa Request for Spouse, undated; 59002 (Box 6, Folder 396)
    - Artist Overview: Michael Ladd, undated; 59001 (Box 6, Folder 397)
    - Michael Ladd Project Description, Poetry Samples, undated; 59000 (Box 6, Folder 398)
    - Artist Overview: Bradley McCallum, Witness, undated; 58999 (Box 6, Folder 399)
    - Bradley McCallum, Final Proposal Submission, Promotional Material and Publicity, undated; 58998 (Box 6, Folder 400)
    - Witness Miscellaneous Archival Material, Education Guide, Draft Prepared for IACD, 1999; 58997 (Box 6, Folder 401)
    - Artist Overview: Demetria Royals, Anita Gonzalez, Robbie McCauley, undated; 58996 (Box 6, Folder 402)
    - Final Proposal Submission, Royals, Gonzalez and McCauley, 1999; 58995 (Box 6, Folder 403)
    - Artist Overview: Patricia Williams, Oliver Lake, Issac Julien, undated; 58994 (Box 6, Folder 404)
    - Promotional Material, Obstacle Illusions, Williams and Lake, undated; 58993 (Box 6, Folder 405)
    - Artist Overview: Ping Chong, 1999; 58992 (Box 6, Folder 406)
    - Ping Chong Rehearsal Notes, Summer 1999, 58991 (Box 6, Folder 407)
    - Ping Chong, Pojagi: Between a Rock and a Hard Place, Promotional Materials, undated; 58990 (Box 6, Folder 408)
    - Ping Chong, Words and Morphology Related to Pojagi, undated; 58989 (Box 6, Folder 409)
    - Final Proposal Submission, Art Spiegelman, 1999; 58988 (Box 6, Folder 410)
    - Gossip Program, undated; 58987 (Box 6, Folder 411)
    - The Sleeping Beauty Program, undated; 58986 (Box 6, Folder 412)
    - The Sleeping Beauty, Panelist Biographies, undated; 58985 (Box 6, Folder 413)
    - The Sleeping Beauty Reference Materials, 1999; 58984 (Box 6, Folder 414)
    - The Sleeping Beauty Reference Materials, 1999; 58983 (Box 6, Folder 415)
    - National Convening, "Animating Democracy: The Artistic Imagination as a Force in Civic Dialogue", A Report to the Ford Foundation, undated; 58982 (Box 6, Folder 416)
    - National Convening, "A Conversation with a Center, Not Sides", undated; 58981 (Box 6, Folder 417)
    - National Convening, "Democracy's Discontent: America in Search of a Public Philosophy", Michael J. Sandel, undated; 58980 (Box 6, Folder 418)
    - National Convening, July 29-31, Participant Biographies, 1999; 58979 (Box 6, Folder 419)
    - National Convening Promotional Statements, undated; 58978 (Box 6, Folder 420)